skyvegas.com 2011-05-12

# Help & Support

**Privacy**

Our Privacy Policy gives info about how we keep your information safe and secure. It outlines what happens to Cookies on your computer, what info we need from you and how we'll treat it and keep your data secure.

**Cookies**

Please be aware that information and data may be automatically collected through the use of Cookies. "Cookies" are small text files that store basic information that a web site can use to recognise repeat site visits, e.g. recall your User ID if this has been previously supplied. We may use this to track behaviour and compile aggregate data in order to improve the web sites, target advertising and assess general effectiveness of such advertising.

Cookies do not attach to your system or damage your files. If you do not want information collected through the use of Cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the Cookie feature. Note, however, that "personalised" services may be affected if the cookie option is disabled.

**Data Collection**

To be able to deposit funds and place bets on the web site, you will be asked to register by entering a User ID and PIN. Such user information will only be used for the purposes as set out in this Privacy Policy.

By entering your user information, you accept that we may retain your user information and that it may be held by us or any third party company which processes it on our behalf.

We reserve the right to perform statistical analyses of user's behaviour and characteristics in order to measure interest in, and use of, the various areas of the web site and, in addition, to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to or who have clicked on their advertising banners. We will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties.

**Disclosure**

We shall be entitled to make available your user information in order to send you information about us and our affiliates, associated companies and organisations, for the following purposes including but not limited to: 

Promotional and/or marketing material about products, services and offers 

Market research or compliance 

Transfers to third parties as required and 

Any requirements imposed by operational law

We are not responsible for any actions or policies of any third parties who request your user information and users should check the applicable privacy policy of such third parties.

**Security**

Security is very important to us. Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") encryption technology is used for protection of information in transit for any sensitive transactions such as payments and withdrawals. Additional security procedures are in place to protect the confidentiality, integrity and availability of your user information. Your user information will not be kept longer than is necessary for the purposes at the collection point or as stated in this Privacy Policy.

**Updates**

You may notify us of any updates, amendments and corrections to previously collected user information by contacting us by email or by entering the "Personal Details" section in "My Account" on [www.skybet.com](http://www.skybet.com/) and entering the relevant changes. Further, upon your request, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete your user information from our database; however, it may be impossible to delete your entry without some residual information remaining because of back-ups and records of deletions.

**Law Enforcement Reporting**

We and our regulators are entitled to share the information we hold on you (which includes personal data and betting history) with regulatory bodies, sporting bodies and other bodies, including the police, in order to investigate suspected fraud, money laundering or sports integrity issues and to comply with our regulatory duties under the the Alderney Gambling Control Commission. 

**Privacy Queries**

Any queries or comments about our Privacy Policy should be forwarded to [dpoffice@bskyb.com](mailto:dpoffice@bskyb.com). Any web site that you may connect to from the site is not covered by this Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right, at any time, to modify, alter, or update this Privacy Policy.
